viralhax.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy - Viral Hax

### Who Are We?

Our website address is **www.viralhax.com**. Website/organization name is **Viralhax**. The behind this website is Jitender Singh. If you want to contact us for any type of query you can email us at- viralhax0@gmail.com. Or use our contact us page.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

If you contact us we will use your name and email address to reply to your query and we won’t share that information with the third parties.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day. Read below to know how we use cookies.

### Use Of Cookies

Our Site viralhax.com uses cookies for several purposes.

  * User Account Login
  * Google Analytics cookies for web site statistics
  * Google Adsense cookies for Google Ads published on the site
  * Social Networking services badges and sharing functionality
  * We use this Adsense codes and analytic for providing you better results.

By visiting our website you agree to use all those cookies which are mentioned above.

We are not spying anyone personal data or when you are using our site. We don’t share anything or any information to anyone. Because we care your about your privacy

You can simply Opt Out From Google Analytic Code For All Sites. You can also opt out from Google AdSense Cookies.

### Disclaimer

Viralhax.com is my personal space where I write about various topics like Apk, Tech, Android and Reviews of different products. I make sure that whatever content I write is helpful to my reader. All content provided on this blog is for informational purposes only. Being the owner of this blog I make no representations as to the accuracy or completeness of any information on this site.

The owner will not be held responsible for any errors or omissions in the information provided on the blog, nor for the availability of this information. Also the blog owner will not be held responsible for any losses, injuries, or damages from the display or use of this information. All opinions expressed on this blog and also in the guest posts are solely those of its authors and do not gives the opinions of any organizations or any affiliates or Viralhax.com.

You are not allowed to reproduce, reprint or publish any part of this blog without written consent from the blog owner.

The contents of this blog are not intended to malign any religion, ethnic group, club, organization, company, or individual.

We are very much concerned about the privacy of your personal information. We collect the information but **WE NEVER SELL** it to third parties.

We also use third party advertisements on Viralhax.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google Adsense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

### USES OF YOUR INFORMATION:

Personal information is used for the following purposes:

– To personalize user experience  
– To improve our Site  
– To improve customer service  
– To send periodic email

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Viralhax.com reserves the right to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will notify it on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Hereby, you acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review privacy policy as and when and be aware of the changes made.

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

We use Complete Analytics Optimization Suite (CAOS) plugin to collect user behavior on our website so that we can improve the performance.

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### Your contact information

If you want to contact us then you can fill our contact us page or you can email us at **viralhax0@gmail.com**

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

We are using Cloudflare SSL on our website and everything which you send to us is with us and the data won’t be shared with any third party.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

If there is data breach we will contact the subscribers that there was a data breach and we will write an email to them whose data is lost.

### What third parties we receive data from

We receive data from Google AdSense and Google Analytics about the user behavior.

### Contact Us

If you still have any questions or suggestions feel free to ask us using below information.

Mail:-  **admin@viralhax.com**  or  **Viralhax0@gmail.com**  
Name:- Jitender Singh
